{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..22.off2.17__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073959825","data":{"timestamp":" 947073959825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 27556ee2-3314-42f2-9b07-056f8037ba4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073970180","data":{"timestamp":" 947073970180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 27556ee2-3314-42f2-9b07-056f8037ba4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073981158","data":{"timestamp":" 947073981158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 27556ee2-3314-42f2-9b07-056f8037ba4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073992178","data":{"timestamp":" 947073992177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 36e4f985-b37c-4288-849e-851c3233cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073992404","data":{"timestamp":" 947073992404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 36e4f985-b37c-4288-849e-851c3233cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073993373","data":{"timestamp":" 947073993372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 36e4f985-b37c-4288-849e-851c3233cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073993927","data":{"timestamp":" 947073993927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 36e4f985-b37c-4288-849e-851c3233cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073994012","data":{"timestamp":" 947073994012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 36e4f985-b37c-4288-849e-851c3233cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074005408","data":{"timestamp":" 947074005408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074042463","data":{"timestamp":" 947074042463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074057154","data":{"timestamp":" 947074057154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074059291","data":{"timestamp":" 947074059291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074069888","data":{"timestamp":" 947074069888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074071327","data":{"timestamp":" 947074071326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074081786","data":{"timestamp":" 947074081786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074089937","data":{"timestamp":" 947074089937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074104433","data":{"timestamp":" 947074104433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074107827","data":{"timestamp":" 947074107827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074120039","data":{"timestamp":" 947074120039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074123042","data":{"timestamp":" 947074123042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074155351","data":{"timestamp":" 947074155351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074166557","data":{"timestamp":" 947074166556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074173536","data":{"timestamp":" 947074173536"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074175129","data":{"timestamp":" 947074175129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074182168","data":{"timestamp":" 947074182168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074185634","data":{"timestamp":" 947074185634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 9bdc5069-c6d0-4973-9bf6-37f343869e8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074204368","data":{"timestamp":" 947074204368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074217097","data":{"timestamp":" 947074217097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074219607","data":{"timestamp":" 947074219607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074226928","data":{"timestamp":" 947074226927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074228235","data":{"timestamp":" 947074228235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074235327","data":{"timestamp":" 947074235327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074241279","data":{"timestamp":" 947074241279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074243137","data":{"timestamp":" 947074243137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074253281","data":{"timestamp":" 947074253281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074256848","data":{"timestamp":" 947074256848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074265498","data":{"timestamp":" 947074265498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074268013","data":{"timestamp":" 947074268013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074277956","data":{"timestamp":" 947074277956"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074289469","data":{"timestamp":" 947074289469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074291796","data":{"timestamp":" 947074291796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074306494","data":{"timestamp":" 947074306494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074308597","data":{"timestamp":" 947074308597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074321424","data":{"timestamp":" 947074321424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074328016","data":{"timestamp":" 947074328016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.we.rand.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074335660","data":{"timestamp":" 947074335660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074343875","data":{"timestamp":" 947074343874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074352098","data":{"timestamp":" 947074352098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074357664","data":{"timestamp":" 947074357663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" 0b7ae647-b6bb-4bbb-9876-785239f42f04"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074377412","data":{"timestamp":" 947074377412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kiko_yowe-kiko-sifa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiko"," userResponse":" kiko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074388935","data":{"timestamp":" 947074388935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hili_geni-saba-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hili"," userResponse":" hili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074408407","data":{"timestamp":" 947074408407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hawa_nazo-kasa-hawa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hawa"," userResponse":" nazo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074418157","data":{"timestamp":" 947074418157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hawa_nazo-kasa-hawa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hawa"," userResponse":" hawa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074430478","data":{"timestamp":" 947074430478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_hula-tuna-pale"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuna"," userResponse":" tuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074441438","data":{"timestamp":" 947074441438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_goso-ziwa-kuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuna"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074452812","data":{"timestamp":" 947074452812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tisa_koti-tisa-saba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tisa"," userResponse":" tisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074461633","data":{"timestamp":" 947074461633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_lima-tope-hiki"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lima"," userResponse":" lima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074470529","data":{"timestamp":" 947074470528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sana_sana-hema-nazo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sana"," userResponse":" hema"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074479347","data":{"timestamp":" 947074479347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sana_sana-hema-nazo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sana"," userResponse":" sana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074487565","data":{"timestamp":" 947074487565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bali_tuzo-bali-goso"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bali"," userResponse":" bali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074496758","data":{"timestamp":" 947074496758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngwe_mito-nchi-ngwe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngwe"," userResponse":" ngwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074500921","data":{"timestamp":" 947074500921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_150503"," gameId":" ca19d767-81be-488c-9fac-b99f1806a5c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngwe_mito-nchi-ngwe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}